Guide to the Records of Religious and Benevolent Societies, Organizations, and Meetings
Yale University Divinity School Library
- D-G
  - Female Bible Society of Philadelphia, 1847 (Box 47)
    Subject Categories: Women's societies; Bible and tract societies
  - Female Bible, Prayer-Book and Tract Society (Box 34)
  - Female Charitable Society of Williamstown (MA)
    SEE: Auxiliary Society for Promoting Good Morals
  - Female Juvenile Mite Society, 1822 (Box 8)
    Subject Categories: Connecticut societies; Women's societies
  - Fides Muni Organization, n.d. (Box 34)
  - Field Lane Ragged Schools, Servants' Home and Night Refugees for the Homeless Poor, 1866 (Box 8)
  - Free Church Abstainers' Society, 1854 (Box 8)
  - Free Tract Society (Interdenominational), n.d. (Box 34)
  - Freedom Club of Downtown Chicago, c.1954 (Box 45)
  - French and Foreign Bible Society, 1857 (Box 47)
  - Friendly Union of Montreal For Suppressing Vice and Promoting Useful Knowledge, 1841 (Box 34)
    Place of Publication: Montreal
    Subject Categories: Societal reform; Christian education/ministry
  - Friends of Democracy, Inc., 1939 (Box 34)
    Place of Publication: Kansas City
    Comments: Pamphlet re. Roman Catholic persecution in Nazi Germany
  - Friends of Europe, 1934, 1937 (Box 8)
  - General Conference of Unitarian and Other Christian Churches, 1923 (Box 34)
    Subject Categories: Connecticut societies; Ecumenical movements; Conferences, conventions
  - General Protestant Episcopal Sunday School Union and Church Book Society, 1827-1859 (Box 34)
  - General Union for Promoting the Observance of the Christian Sabbath, 1829-1831 (Box 34)
  - German Evangelical Aid Society, 1900 (Box 34)
  - Girls' Friendly Society of the U.S.A. (Box 34)
  - Glasgow Auxiliary Bible Society, 1820 (Box 9)
    Place of Publication: Glasgow
  - Glasgow Voluntary Church Society, 1832 (Box 34)
  - Gloucestershire Association of Baptist Churches, 1846 (Box 34)
    Place of Publication: Gloucester
  - Gospel Tract Society, 1835 (Box 34)
  - Greenock Voluntary Church Association, 1835 (Box 34)
    Place of Publication: Greenock, U.K.
  - Guardians of Liberty, c.1921 (Box 45)
  - Guild of the Pope's Peace, 1916 (Box 34)
    Place of Publication: Oxford
- H-K
  - Hampshire Bible Society, 1823 (Box 47)
    Place of Publication: Northampton, MA
  - Hampshire Charitable Society, 1815-1816 (Box 9)
    Place of Publication: Hampshire Co., MA
  - Hampshire Sabbath School Union, 1839 (Box 34)
  - Hampshire Society for Promoting Religion in the County and its Vicinity, 1814 (Box 9)
    Place of Publication: Chichester, U.K.
  - Hannah Gray Home, New Haven, 1910-1946 (Box 51)
    Biographical / Historical
    Hannah Gray was an African American seamstress in New Haven who upon her death in 1861 bequeathed her home for the use of indigent elderly women of color. The Home was supported and run by the Women's Twentieth Century Club. The Hannah Gray home continues to serve low-income elderly persons in need of residential care.
    Material includes correspondence, reports, committee records, fundraising and financial records, operational documents.
  - Harmony Conference of Churches, n.d. (Box 34)
  - Helping Hand Association, 1869-1870 (Box 45)
  - Hereford Protestant Association, 1835 (Box 34)
    Place of Publication: Hereford, U.K.
  - Hexham Sabbath School Union, 1819 (Box 34)
    Place of Publication: Hexham, U.K.
  - Hibernian Bible Society, 1826-1936 (Box 48)
  - Holiness Alliance, 1879 (Box 34)
    Subject Categories: Ecumenical movements; Sects, religious societies
  - Home for Women, 1871 (Box 45)
  - Human Relations Council of Greater New Haven, Inc., 1968 (Box 21)
  - Husbands' and Fathers' Association, 1843 (Box 9)
  - Incorporated Church Building Society, 1853 (Box 34)
  - Indian Rights Association, 1940 (Box 9)
  - Institute of Social Order, 1943 (Box 34)
  - Institution of Protestant Deaconesses, 1911 (Box 36)
    Place of Publication: Pennsylvania
    Comments: Report re. Lutheran Deaconess Motherhouse
  - Intercollegiate Zionist Association of America, 1917 (Box 34)
  - Intercouncil Field Department, 1947/1948 (Box 21)
  - Interdenominational Commission of Maine, 1894, 1910 (Box 35)
    Place of Publication: Maine
  - Interdenominational Commission of New Hampshire, 1907 (Box 35)
  - International Bible Students Association
    SEE: Watchtower Bible and Tract Society
  - International Catholic Truth Society, n.d. (Box 35)
  - International Christian Moral Science Association, n.d. (Box 42)
    Place of Publication: Great Britain
    Subject Categories: United Kingdom; Societal reform
  - International Christian Workers' Association, 1892, n.d. (Box 22)
    Place of Publication: Springfield, MA New Haven
    Subject Categories: Christian education/ministry; Connecticut societies
  - International Conference of Bible Translators, 1947 (Box 48)
    Place of Publication: Zeist, Netherlands ("Woudschoten")
    Subject Categories: Bible and tract societies; Conferences, conventions
  - International Congress of the World Fellowship of Faiths, 1936 (Box 9)
  - International Congress on Sunday Rest, 1894 (Box 35)
  - International Council of Free Christians and Other Religious Liberals, 1913 (Box 35)
  - International Council of Religious Education, 1927-1950, n.d. (Box 9)
  - International Council of Religious Education (Box 10)
  - International Council on Biblical Inerrancy, 1987 (Box 45)
  - International Federation of Lord's Day Societies, 1880-1881 (Box 10)
  - International Legion of the Cross, 1944-1945 (Box 35)
    Place of Publication: Auckland, New Zealand
  - International Order of the King's Daughters and Sons (Connecticut Branch), 1896 (Box 35)
  - International Society of Christian Endeavor, 1931, n.d. (Box 35)
  - International Sunday School Association, 1918 (Box 11)
  - International Sunday School Council of Religious Education, 1922-1923 (Box 11)
  - International Union of Liberal Christian Women, 1930 (Box 11)
    Subject Categories: United Kingdom; Women's societies
  - Interseminary Movement in the United States, 1929, 1943-1944 (Box 11)
    SEE ALSO: Student Association of the Middle Atlantic Theological Seminaries
  - Irish Society for Promoting the Scriptural Education and Religious Instruction of Irish Roman Catholics, 1859 (Box 11)
  - Jewish Vegetarian Society of New York, 1942 (Box 45)
  - John C. Collins Association, 1877, 1879 (Box 21)
    SEE ALSO: New Haven Gospel Union
  - King's Head Society for Educating Young Men for the Work of the Ministry among Protestant Dissenters, 1813 (Box 54)
  - Knights of Columbus, 1916 (Box 35)
    Place of Publication: Davenport, Iowa
- L-M
  - Labor and Neighbor, 1880 (Box 35)
  - Labourers' Tract Society, 1834 (Box 35)
  - Ladies' American Home Education Society and Temperance Union, 1857 (Box 11)
    Subject Categories: Women's societies; Christian education/ministry Societal reform
  - Ladies' Christian Association, 1858 (Box 35)
  - Ladies' Christian Commissions, 1864 (Box 22)
  - Ladies' Christian Union of the City of New York, 1865-1886 (Box 11)
  - Ladies' Hibernian Female School Society, 1857 (Box 35)
    Subject Categories: United Kingdom; Women's societies; Christian education/ministry
  - Ladies' Relief Agency, 1874 (Box 35)
    Subject Categories: Women's societies; Relief and charitable societies
  - Ladies' Religious Publication Society, 1860 (Box 35)
    Place of Publication: Albany
  - Lambeth Conference, 1888 (Box 11)
    Place of Publication: Lambeth, U.K.
  - Latin Historical Society, 1893 (Box 35)
  - Lawrence Memorial Association, 1899 (Box 35)
  - League for the Protection of the Family, 1897 (Box 35)
  - Liberal Catholic Union, n.d. (Box 22)
    Place of Publication: North Somercotes, Lincs.
  - Liberal Tract Society, n.d. (Box 11)
    Place of Publication: Worcester, MA
  - Life's Estate, Ltd. of California, 1939 (Box 35)
    Place of Publication: Denver
  - Liverpool Mariners' Church Society, 1828 (Box 11)
    Place of Publication: Liverpool, U.K.
  - Liverpool Protestant Association, 1839 (Box 11)
  - Living Stream Ministry / or The Local Church - writings of its founder, Witness Lee, 1968-1985 (Box 25–27, Box 58–59)
    Place of Publication: Anaheim, CA
    Box 25: 1968-1981; Box 26: 1984 Box 27: 1984; Box 58: 1985
  - London Cabmen's Lord's Day Rest Association, 1862 (Box 12)
    Subject Categories: United Kingdom; Sabbath observance
  - London Congregational Chapel-Building Society, 1850-1856 (Box 35)
  - London Diocesan Church Building Society, 1855-1858 (Box 35)
  - London Hibernian Society for Establishing Schools and Circulating the Holy Scriptures in Ireland, 1807-1830 (Box 36)
  - London Maternal Association, 1836 (Box 36)
    Subject Categories: Women's societies; United Kingdom
  - London Missionary and Tract Society of the New Jerusalem Church, 1829, 1831 (Box 36)
    Comments: Swedenborgian
  - London Religious Tract Society, 1803 (Box 36)
  - Long Island Bible Society, 1855-1856, 1859 (Box 47)
  - Lord's Day Alliance of Canada, n.d. (Box 36)
    Place of Publication: Toronto
  - Lord's Day Society, 1833-1834, 1845 (Box 12)
  - Loughborough and Ashby Protestant Tract Society (Box 38)
    Place of Publication: Loughborough
  - Lux Mundi Group, 1956 (Box 12)
  - Maine Convention of Universalists, 1851 (Box 36)
    Place of Publication: Turner
  - Mangrol Jain Sabha, 1906 (Box 36)
    Place of Publication: Bombay
    Comments: vegetarian society
  - Marine Bible Society of New Haven, 1827 (Box 22)
  - Marine Bible Society of New York, 1817 (Box 47)
  - Maryland Tract Society, 1918 (Box 36)
  - Marylebone Mothers' Union, 1903 (Box 36)
  - Massachusetts Sabbath School Society, 1825-1859 (Box 12)
  - Maternal Association, 1816 (Box 36)
    Place of Publication: Portland Boston
  - Maternal Association of Union Church, n.d. (Box 36)
  - Meeting of Benevolent Societies of Hampshire County, MA, 1838 Oct 18 (Box 24)
    Subject Categories: Relief and charitable societies; Conferences, conventions
  - Men and Religion Forward Movement, 1912 (Box 36)
  - Merrimack Bible Society, 1910 (Box 47)
    Place of Publication: Newburyport
  - Metropolis Churches' Fund, 1837-1853 (Box 36)
  - Midnight Mission, 1873 (Box 45)
  - Moral Re-Armament, 1939, n.d. (Box 54)
    Place of Publication: London New York
  - Murray Grove Association (Universalist), 1887 (Box 36)
- N
  - Nassau-Hall Bible Society, 1813-1814, 1821 (Box 12)
    Place of Publication: Princeton, NJ
  - National Armenian Relief Committee, 1897-1898 (Box 36)
    Place of Publication: Andover, MA; Barre, MA
  - National Bible Society of Scotland, 1870-1896 (Box 12)
  - National Catholic Welfare Conference, c.1943, n.d. (Box 36)
  - National Club, 1846-1856 (Box 36)
  - National Commission on Consultations about Student Christian Work, 1935 (Box 12)
  - National Conference of Charities and Correction, 1895 May 24-30 (Box 36)
    Subject Categories: Connecticut societies; Relief and charitable societies; Conferences, conventions
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews (or Jews and Christians), 1932, 1937, 1943-1944 (Box 12)
    Subject Categories: Ecumenical movements; Related to Jews
  - National Conference on the Christian Way of Life, 1922-1925 (Box 44)
  - National Congress of Mothers, 1909 (Box 36)
  - National Council of Student Christian Associations, 1931, 1941, n.d. (Box 12)
  - National Council on Religion in Higher Education, 1923-1934, n.d. (Box 12)
  - National Federation of Churches and Christian Workers (Box 36)
  - National Lord's Day Convention, 1844 Nov 27-28 (Box 36)
    Subject Categories: Sabbath observance; Conferences, conventions
  - National Religion and Labor Foundation, 1948 (Box 36)
  - National Religious Liberty Association, 1890s (Box 36)
  - National Society (for Promoting the Education of the Poor in the Principles of the Established Church), 1839-1858 (Box 36)
    Place of Publication: Westminster, U.K.
  - National Sunday School Convention of the U.S., 1869 (Box 44)
    Place of Publication: Newark, NJ
  - National Temperance Society, n.d. (Box 45)
  - National Women's Christian Temperance Union, 1896, 1911-1912, 1927, n.d. (Box 12)
    Place of Publication: Chicago Evanston
    Subject Categories: Societal reform; Women's societies
  - Naval and Military Bible Society, 1831 (Box 47)
  - New Bedford Port Society, 1914 (Box 12)
    Place of Publication: New Bedford
    Subject Categories: Relief and charitable societies; Christian education/ministry
  - New Bedford Tract and Book Society, 1825 (Box 37)
  - New Britain Tract Society, 1872 (Box 37)
    Place of Publication: New Britain
  - New England Assembly, 1881 (Box 37)
  - New England Deaconess Association, 1902-1913 (Box 12)
    Comments: Methodist Episcopal Association
  - New England Fellowship, 1939 (Box 21)
    Comments: Association of evangelical denominations
  - New England Home for Little Wanderers, 1904 (Box 37)
  - New England Sabbath Protective League, 1896 (Box 37)
  - New England Sabbath School Union, 1836, 1840 (Box 37)
  - New England Tract Society, 1813-1822 (Box 13)
    Place of Publication: Andover
  - New Hampshire Bible Society, 1814 (Box 47)
  - New Haven Baptist Association, 1910, 1917 (Box 21)
  - New Haven Center for Continuing Education for the Ministry, 1965 (Box 44)
  - New Haven City Religious Services Directory, 1878, 1882, 1883 (Box 24)
  - New Haven Clerical Association, 1938 (Box 21)
  - New Haven Council of Churches, 1945 (Box 21)
  - New Haven County Bible Society, 1830, n.d. (Box 21)
  - New Haven County Sabbath School Union, 1832 (Box 37)
  - New Haven County Sunday School Association, 1914 (Box 13)
  - New Haven Evangelization Union of the Methodist Episcopal Church, 1894/1895 (Box 21)
  - New Haven Gospel Union, 1879-1885, n.d. (Box 21)
    SEE ALSO: John C. Collins Association
  - New Haven Sunday School Union, 1856-1872 (Box 21)
  - New Haven Sunday Schools Rally, 1897 May 31, 1900 May 30 (Box 24)
    Subject Categories: Connecticut societies; Christian education/ministry Conferences, conventions
  - New Haven Women's Church Union, 1932 (Box 21)
  - New Jersey Bible Society, 1810-1812 (Box 13)
    Place of Publication: Trenton
  - New Jersey Sunday School Association, 1863, 1872 (Box 13)
    Place of Publication: Newark
  - New York Bethel Union, 1821, 1833 (Box 13)
    Comments: work among seamen
  - New York Bible Society, 1810-1931 (Box 47)
  - New York Bible and Common Prayer Book Society, 1858, 1869 (Box 13)
  - New York City Maternal Association, 1839-1845 (Box 37)
  - New York Civic League, 1914 (Box 45)
  - New York Female Auxiliary Bible Society, 1818-1882 (Box 58)
  - New York Female Bible Society, 1818-1883 (Box 22)
  - New York Female Union Society for the Promotion of Sabbath Schools, 1818, 1823 (Box 13)
    Subject Categories: Women's societies; Christian education/ministry
  - New York Protestant Episcopal Tract Society, 1829-1833 (Box 37)
  - New York Reformation Quadricentenary Committee, 1917 (Box 37)
  - New York Religious Tract Society, 1818, 1823 (Box 13)
  - New York Sabbath Committee, 1857-1905, n.d. (Box 13)
  - New York Sabbath Tract Society, 1844 (Box 37)
  - New York State Church Federation Society, n.d. (Box 37)
  - New York State Conference of Religion, 1903 (Box 37)
  - New York Sunday School Association, 1874-1902 (Box 13)
  - New York Sunday School Institute, 1867-1868 (Box 44)
  - New York Sunday School Teachers' Association, 1869 (Box 44)
    Place of Publication: Rochester, NY
  - New York Sunday School Union Society, 1818-1861, n.d. (Box 22)
  - New York Young Men's Society, 1831 (Box 37)
  - Newfoundland School Society, 1828 (Box 37)
    Subject Categories: Christian education/ministry; United Kingdom
  - Norfolk Bible Society, 1815 (Box 47)
    Place of Publication: Norfolk, VA
  - Norfolk and Norwich Protestant Association, 1841 (Box 37)
    Place of Publication: Norwich, U.K.
  - North American Ecumenical Youth Assembly, 1961 (Box OV-d)
    Phonograph recording
  - North London Deaconesses' Institution, 1866, n.d. (Box 37)
  - Northfield Summer Conferences, 1902 (Box 37)
    Place of Publication: Northfield, MA
- O-R
  - Oneida Bible Society, 1813-1814 (Box 14)
    Place of Publication: Utica, NY
  - Open Air Workers' Association of America, 1894 (Box 37)
  - Orange County Bible Society, 1912-1927 (Box 47)
  - Orthodox Christian Educational Society, 1950 (Box 21)
  - Otsego County Bible Society, 1813-1814 (Box 14)
    Place of Publication: Cooperstown, NY
  - Oxford Group, 1934-1935 (Box 14)
    Place of Publication: Oxford London
  - Parent Education Society of the Evangelical Lutheran Church, n.d. (Box 14)
  - Parker Society, 1841, 1850 (Box 37)
  - Pastoral Union of Connecticut, 1854 (Box 37)
    Place of Publication: Wethersfield (?)
  - Pennsylvania Bible Society, 1906 (Box 47)
  - Philadelphia Bible Society, 1813 (Box 48)
  - Philanthropic Society, 1807, 1828 (Box 37)
  - Philip Schaff Memorial Committee, 1913 (Box 38)
  - Prayer Book and Homily Society, 1828-1853 (Box 14)
  - Preachers' Retreat Association, c.1888 (Box 37)
  - Presentist Society, 1923 (Box 37)
  - Protestant Association, 1836, 1838 (Box 37)
  - Protestant Bible Society of Paris, 1827 (Box 54)
  - Protestant Episcopal Society for the Promotion of Evangelical Knowledge, 1851-1911 (Box 37)
  - Protestant Episcopal Tract Society, 1840-1877, n.d. (Box 38)
  - Protestant Union for the Defence and Support of the Protestant Religion and the British Constitution, 1813 (Box 14)
  - Queen's Work, 1933-1941 (Box 38)
    Place of Publication: St. Louis
    Subject Categories: Bible and tract societies; Related to Roman Catholicism
  - Religio-Scientific Institute, 1920 (Box 38)
  - Religion and Welfare Recovery, c.1934 (Box 38)
  - Religious Attendance League, 1941 (Box 54)
  - Religious Charitable Society and Conference of Churches of Middlesex North and Vicinity, 1856 (Box 38)
    Place of Publication: Fitchburg, MA
  - Religious Education Association, 1903-1919 (Box 14)
  - Religious Education Federation, 1916 (Box 14)
  - Religious Tract Society, 1835-1848, n.d. (Box 39)
  - Religious Tract Society of the City of Washington, 1827 (Box 38)
  - Religious Tract and Book Society for Ireland, 1833, 1838 (Box 14)
  - Religious Tract and Book Society for Scotland, 1835 (Box 14)
  - Rensselaer County Bible Society, 1838-1840 (Box 48)
    Place of Publication: Troy, NY
  - Report of Franklin County Benevolent Societies, 1839 (Box 24)
    Place of Publication: Greenfield, MA
  - Revival Tract Society, n.d. (Box 38)
- S
  - Sabbath Alliance, 1849, n.d. (Box 14)
  - Sabbath Convention, 1842 Jul 20-21 (Box 24)
  - Sabbath Day Convention, 1844 (Box 38)
    Place of Publication: Columbus, OH
  - Sabbath Observance Society, 1896-1897 (Box 38)
  - Sabbath Protection Society, 1833 (Box 14)
  - Sabbath School Celebration at Sachem's Wood, 1840 Jul 4 (Box 24)
  - Sabbath School Teachers' Society of the First Presbyterian Church, Newark, 1833 (Box 38)
  - Science League of America, 1926 (Box 45)
    Place of Publication: San Francisco
    Comments: re. evolution question
  - Scottish Disestablishment Association, 1875-1876 (Box 14)
  - Scottish Episcopal Church Society, 1848 (Box 14)
  - Scriptural Knowledge Institution for Home and Abroad, 1867 (Box 14)
  - Scripture Readers' Society for Ireland, 1834 (Box 14)
  - Sea Cliff Bible Conference, 1902 (Box 38)
    Place of Publication: Sea Cliff, L.I.
  - Segye Kidokkyo T'ongil Sillyong Hyophoe (Unification Church), c.1965-1974 (Box 19)
  - Self-Realization Fellowship, 1934 (Box 38)
  - Silent Evangelism Association, n.d. (Box 38)
    Place of Publication: Battle Creek, MI
  - Silent Evangelist Tract Society, n.d. (Box 38)
  - Société Saint Augustin, n.d. (Box 38)
    Place of Publication: Bruges, Belgium
    Comments: marketing religious artwork/photographs
  - Société de la Morale Chrétienne, 1825 (Box 46)
  - Société des Écoles du Dimanche du Canton de Vaud, 1879, 1911 (Box 14)
    Place of Publication: Lausanne
  - Société des Livres Religieux de Toulouse, 1851 (Box 38)
    Place of Publication: Toulouse
  - Société des Traités Religieux de Paris, 1830-1831 (Box 38)
  - Society for Bettering the Condition of the Poor, 1803 (Box 40)
  - Society for Promoting Christian Instruction in London and its Vicinity, 1834, n.d. (Box 14)
  - Society for Promoting Christian Knowledge, 1802-1858, n.d. (Box 41–42)
  - Society for Promoting Female Education in the East, 1844 (Box 40)
  - Society for Promoting Religious Instruction in the Isle of Shoals, 1823 (Box 15)
    Place of Publication: Newburyport, MA
  - Society for Promoting Religious Knowledge, 1846 (Box 40)
  - Society for Promoting Theological Education, 1832, 1860 (Box 15)
  - Society for Promoting the Employment of Additional Curates in Populous Places, 1838, 1857 (Box 46)
  - Society for Promoting the Study of Religions, 1931 (Box 40)
  - Society for Protecting the Rights of Conscience in Ireland, 1852 (Box 40)
  - Society for the Abolition of the Blasphemy Laws, 1924 (Box 40)
  - Society for the Diffusion of Useful and Religious Knowledge among the Italians, 1842 (Box 40)
  - Society for the Education and Advancement of Young Seamen, 1864 (Box 40)
  - Society for the Elucidation of Religious Principles, 1935-1936 (Box 14)
  - Society for the Extension of Liberal Knowledge, 1920 (Box 40)
  - Society for the Home Study of Holy Scripture and Church History, 1892 (Box 40)
  - Society for the Increase of the Ministry, 1859 (Box 40)
    Place of Publication: Hartford (?)
  - Society for the Liberation of Religion from State-Patronage and Control, 1854-c.1894 (Box 40)
  - Society for the Promoting Due Observance of the Lord's Day, 1831-1861 (Box 15)
  - Society for the Promotion of Good Will Toward Men, n.d. (Box 40)
    Place of Publication: Summit, NJ
  - Society for the Relief of Aged and Infirm Protestant Dissenting Ministers, 1818-1820 (Box 15)
  - Society for the Relief of Clergymen and the Widows and Children of Clergymen, 1851-1859 (Box 15)
  - Society for the Relief of Poor Pious Clergymen, 1815-1816 (Box 40)
  - Society for the Relief of the Necessitous Widows and Children of Protestant Dissenting Ministers, 1842 (Box 15)
  - Society for the Revival of Convocation, 1851 (Box 40)
  - Society of Biblical Literature and Exegesis, 1880-1930 (Box 40)
  - Society of Charitable Sisters, 1818 (?) (Box 40)
  - Society of Christian Morality, 1823 (Box 40)
  - Society of Silent Unity, n.d. (Box 40)
    Place of Publication: Kansas City, MO
    Comments: spiritual healing
  - Society of St. Johnland, 1870 (Box 38)
  - Society of St. Vincent de Paul, 1848-1884 (Box 40)
    Place of Publication: New York Toronto Mexico
  - Society of Unitarian Christians, Established in the West of England, For Promoting Christian Knowledge, and the Practice of Virtue, By Distributing Books, 1828 (Box 40)
    Place of Publication: Bristol, U.K.
  - Sons and Daughters of Washington, 1923-1926 (Box 45)
  - South Bucks Church Union Society, 1840 (Box 40)
    Place of Publication: Wycombe
  - South Carolina Tract Society, c.1862 (Box 40)
  - South-Western Bible Society of New Orleans, 1850 (Box 48)
    Place of Publication: New Orleans
  - Spanish Place Catholic Literary Society, c.1847 (Box 40)
  - Spiritual Mobilization, Inc. (James W. Fifield), 1940-1951, n.d. (Box 45)
  - St. Albans Branch Bible Society, 1812 (Box 48)
    Place of Publication: St. Albans, U.K.
  - St. John's Guild, 1873, 1893 (Box 38)
  - State Sabbath Convention, 1844 May 30-31 (Box 40)
    Place of Publication: Harrisburg, PA
  - Student Association of the Middle Atlantic Theological Seminaries, 1927-1931 (Box 23)
  - Suffolk Auxiliary Bible Society, 1812 (Box 48)
    Place of Publication: Ipswich, UK
  - Sunday School Council of Evangelical Denominations, 1912, 1920-1921 (Box 15)
  - Sunday School Society (Boston), 1833-1852 (Box 15)